I don't boxing video I guess you could
say I don't really know what you call it
I got these headphones because okay
alright here's my history with
headphones
[Music]
the only headphones I've ever used that
I thought were decent where I got these
like skull candy like little earbuds
they were like 10 bucks they were better
than any cheap headphones I had they
were the last like you know half a year
to rehear depending on how you take care
of them and I was like damn like these
work great then I got a pair of gaming
headphones from Walmart that were like
on sale for 40 bucks and then they
worked pretty good but then they broke
like the the mechanism that goes like
around your headphones that part like
broke like one of the ears like
literally broke off like the top part
and then I got another pair which is the
pair I've been using actually what they
look like oh but the pair I've been
using a crop
these are the headphones that I normally
use and they look like this they're from
Walmart crop they're like these gaming
headphones that I got they say black
web-like warmer brand I didn't even
realize but yeah I mean like they're
really actually super uncomfortable but
they're just super loose on my head
they're constantly like falling off like
when I put them on it's like I can't
there's just they're not tight you know
if I really want to like cancel out the
noise I have to press them pan defeats
the purpose they're not really loud -
really quiet headphones especially like
the only loud if I like I said like if I
press them down and like this thing's
just annoying doesn't ever use it
everything about these headphones is
annoying just everything about them so I
got these headphones these are
headphones I've been looking at for
quite a while it's just what the box
looks like in this box looks like so
like extravagant - and they got like
this like leather handle on it these
headphones had like really good reviews
on Amazon
I mean basically what I was looking for
was like an over the ear headphone noise
cancelling most importantly kind of for
the purpose of recording audio like
listening to the things I create crisp
and I like to not have to hear anything
outside surround sound kind of yeah I
wanted always cancelling headphones and
like I mean these you know they say that
they do that I'm the only complaint I
heard about these were that they were
uncomfortable but if you switch out the
padding because they have like other
pads you can put on that they're
comfortable so I mean but besides that
there really was no complaints also
these headphones are fully customizable
so anything that goes wrong with them
you can get it fixed and but I mean
they're Wireless so when your warranty
they're going to be better than what I
have right now because what I have right
now is the Walmart garbage
they're called v-moda cross feed
wireless headphones and like the casing
is so weird cuz it's like an it's like a
dislike like bent side on both I mean
that's kind of like their whole gig is
aerodynamic looking I don't know
headphone
it's just so beautiful you don't want to
rip it open but this little button when
we
open it like that there's like a ribbon
oh you're supposed to cut the ribbon so
you cut this ribbon
[Music]
okay so movie come in a crease look at
that look how cool that is
and then this is a little thingy that
comes with it Wow look at this case so
you take these out of the box we have
charger for the headphones because
they're bluetooth and then the cord for
them
oh you even have one of these little
attachments that's beautiful for it to
go in interface things off favorite part
of this is it's so cool that comes you
like this case Wow look how like much
moment' like how much movement these
look like they were gonna flick they
think they're gonna fit so good like
they're so comfortable and you hold them
up like this they stay together it'll
stay on your head with it these ones
look at all the space between them this
is why they don't fit way too loose what
is that I have a small head okay please
do not wrap around my head right but
these look like they're going to and I'm
really excited like look at the
difference in the size the size alone
yes the reason I should get them okay
take off this little wrapper on it these
wrappers but I'm better break them into
somehow they got like little protectors
on the outsides that's nice oh yeah oh
my god yes yes they fit me so much
better I think I can tell it there's
something going on that I can't really
and I bet there's Sun coming up as I
super can't like wow that looks like
that's where you're charged on and then
that's where the court goes and if you
want to use the cord but look at the
difference like these are the ones I've
been using like these pieces of crap
they're super loose super uncomfortable
like sure you were my ears
here's what my ears are then these
puppies new suction right on there with
my ear fits inside line of these things
like making myself would like don't fit
around my ears at all like a glove like
dude
my ears are half on and half knots I
mean if I try to make them like super
small like you know no these just come
down to compare yes yes oh my god I'm so
excited I'm gonna go test these out
because I'm really excited only I did
some videos go check back with them and
everything well I really gotta go pee I
want to go crazy I just want to hear it
they sound like awesome to them are they
quickly can i plug this in here oh my
god dude you sound better than a
computer yes yes and the volume on my
computer is on like all-time low with
this music but uh I check in later
[Music]
hey guys I'm back okay so I'm back yes
so alright musics I'm James James hey
guys these headphones I have been using
these for like the last week or so like
editing and messing around with them
they're great right like they're super
noise-isolating which is what I wanted
and all I gotta say is they're great
they are they're great but how do I put
this all the reviews were right
which makes me kind disappointed but
like if you might remember earlier on
the video I said that there was all good
reviews except for this one thing that
kept popping up people saying they're
uncomfortable and I was thinking like I
have a big head you know they're gonna
be comfortable right I wasn't really
worried about that cuz I'm so used to my
headphones like not working or like
sticking to my head at all but like
these stick to your head so much that
they aren't comfortable it's when I wear
my glasses it like presses my glasses
like it's just like this parts really
tight Melissa why would you buy
headphones if there's always reviews
saying that they're uncomfortable a
worst case scenario I'll just have to
buy extra yeah whatever I didn't think
it was gonna happen but it did
yeah so basically all these people in
the comments were like yo like you got
to get these cushions just awesome
headphones these were all the comments
awesome headphones I love on the great
the only thing is is they're
uncomfortable as phone I just got myself
some new extra large pads and they work
awesome like that was most of the
comments they're fully customizable
headphones so they have their own pads
that you can buy like v-moda brand pads
that you can switch these out with that
are bigger extra-large v-moda so I'm
gonna jump on the freak train because
these things are uncomfortable I spent a
lot of money on them these came up first
and these are like an off-brand but they
make them so that they fit these and
these had like really really really
reviews on them so the thing right right
beneath these ones was the v-moda brand
and that was like I had way more people
that were using it so like way more
reviews but actually had like lower
stars and it was like just a longer I
mean they both talking like good stars
but like this one was like better and
the only complaint I've ever seen about
these is that they're unattractive
looking like they don't look good on the
headphones they don't look sweet they
look kind of fat I don't care what they
look like I don't give a damn and so
when you open it up it looks like this
and now I'm just gonna see and figure
out if I can figure out to put these on
but yeah they look like this
oh my god there's so many videos on how
to replace these memory cushions you
know why because they suck okay so we're
gonna watch us now and see how we do it
to remove them you grab the other
partner thumb the inner part with your
fingers and you pull towards the middle
from the bottom to kind of pull that
plate away and pull the tabs out this is
showing the orientation you know what
Edwards the middle from the bottom
towards the middle from the bottom kind
of pulled up towards the middle from the
bottom oh my god I don't want to break
them I just did it this is the
comparison you have this is the old pad
that came with them and then this is the
new pad did I just bought so these are
supposed to be way more comfortable
this doesn't they look like like this
the whole is like if you move like that
it's like the difference right there and
these are like the wicked ones
okay don't break it Melissa um like that
puppet of being a bandit ooh boom easy
peace oh just a pain about come on a
second I'll flip the ear oh here we go
like that like so I'm just figuring this
out now put one side in the other side
all right I think I got one in I got ya
I could I could understand why they
think that that's a little ugly but I
like the way it feels it feels like
memory cushiony
[Applause]
you know this is odd they still there's
the same headphones if it still sound
good it still sound the same but I feel
like there's more there's more air
between like my ear and the speakers
it's taking like a longer to get to me
before it was like super like against it
I guess I could say so it's like a
different effect when it goes into your
ear like this one's a little more Airy
kind of not like it's not loud
necessarily but it's just not like as
really in your ear I guess you could say
I don't know it seems like it's gonna
work so let's hope that it does like
smooth you like this video
I have no idea why I made this video I
have to pee and then maybe I'll come
another video because I just
feel like filming something else
long story short guys these headphones
suck
I wouldn't recommend them see you guys
next video peace out guys
[Music]